Guide to the Stanford University, Board of Trustees, Meeting Records SC1010
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records created prior to 2010, 1885-2009; Series 1
  - Supporting material, 1905-1976, 1998-2009; Subseries 3; 28 Linear Feet (56 boxes)
    - Newcomer, A.G. - death of; Tarter purchase (land near Vina bought by Stanford U.); Durham ranch; Spring Valley Water Co. - Searsville Lake; Stanford Court apartments (California & Powell Streets, San Francisco), 1913 Sep 26 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Organ, Memorial Church; Grounds, improvement of (landscaping); Offer of preserved human hand for purchase, with clipping; Academic Council problems, 1913 Sep 26 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Barber, William Burton, Loan Fund; Stanford, Thomas W. and Coover visit; Medical Department; Clark, George T. report of library tour; Treasurer's report; Dickey, W.J. trust; Sly, L.H; Tarter tract; Memorial Church Mosaics, 1913 Oct 31 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Memorial tablet to Profs who died in service to University; High Voltage Lab; Memorial Church: reproductions of apostles in marble niches; Memorial Church: estimate for mosaics; Dr. C. Annette Buckel bequest for fellowship in education; Architect recommended for the new Library: Cram, Goodhue, and Ferguson (ncludes letter of recomendation by John K. Branner); Lane Hospital: extensive survey by M.E. McCalmont, hospital consultant, 1913 Nov 28 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - American Cotton Company Stock; Faculty housing; Dept. of history: request for departmental library, with drawing; Union and Women's club bldg. -lease and other matters; University Architect: Bakewell and Brown; Alfred Mosley gift of geological collection; Electric Power for Vina Ranch; Report on cemetary reinterment, Nov 28, 1913 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Copy of a document re work on Memorial Church; Carpentry work by E. A. Hettinger [copied 2007 at History San Jose], Oct. 1913 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Auditor's Report for fiscal year ending July 31, 1912, 1913 Dec 26 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Architect recommentd for proposed new library building (J. K. Branner letter); LaneHospital: McCalmont report re hospital laundry; Lease for Prof. Campbell and Prof. Allardice; Cemetary transplant, including report on contact with relatives; T.J. Walker: portait of Sen. Stanford for sale (declined); Prof. E.D. Adams, leave of absence; Calistoga Springs property title, 1913 Dec 26 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Workman's Compensation Insurance; Auditor's report, Medical School and Vina Ranch; Vina Ranch water rights; Salary study - H.C. Hoover, 1914 Jan 30 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Medical School: H.C. Hoover recommends that S. U. maintain it; Salviati, Memorial Church mosaics; New York Central RR Co; Cleveland and Pittsburgh bonds; Vina Agency; Memorial Church mosaics; Revised ground lease for faculty housing: H.C. Hoover; Charles Lathrop resigns as business manager, 1914 Jan 30 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Lane Hospital; Bookplate; Bond Audit; Campus residences appraised; 1st published financial report; Patient's Fund; Cemetary reinterment; Option to buy land adjoining Vina Ranch; Medical School report, 1914 Feb 27 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Medical School; State vaccination law, 1914 Mar 27 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Contract for wrecking museum; U.S. Army: rent owed L.S.J.U; Pickett Land purchase; King property purchase; Fee Entry resolution; New Museum building: Art Gallery; Rejection of proposed consolidation of U.C. and Stanford medical schools; Resignation of Vanderlynn Stowe, 1914 Apr 24 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Proposal to take over San Francisco, Polyclinic to be used ofr postdoctoral medical studies; Post Office on campus; "Foothill Blvd."; King Tract purchase; Purchase of land and water rights; Wm H. Welch, President of Johns Hopkins critique of Medical School situation; Death of Charles Lathrop: memorial resolution; City streets on Stanford land; Amalgamation of Medical Schools, 1914 May 29 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Amalgamation of U.C. - Stanford medical schools rejected; Philip K. Brown - grift to medical school; Audit of Charles Lathrop's accounts; Leon Sloss elected to Board of Directors of Pacific Improvement Co. to replace Lathrop; Pacific Improvement Co; Mausoleum; Resolution re access to safety deposit boxes, 1914 Jun 26 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Spring Valley Water Company Conference; Resignation of Dr. Arnold Gessel; Road rights, Butte Co; Sale of Southern Pacific bonds; L.S.J.U. Memorial Scholarship, 1914 Aug 1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Pacific Improvement Co. land purchase; Election of officers of Board of Trustees; T.W. Stanford - Branner correspondence on Medical School, 1914 Aug 28 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Copies of documents re work done on campus, Water pipe to history corner and heating work at Memorial church; copied at history San Jose., 1914 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Official Seal of the University, 1914 Sep 25 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Jewel Fund; New York Railways Co. bonds; Organ repair, 1914 Oct 30 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Branner Library purchased; Vina Ranch, water rights; City of Palo Alto - land lease; N.E.A. endowment for Medical School; Removal of statue"Faith" from Oval to mark spot of old cemetary; Southern Pacific Stock, 1914 Nov 27 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Reservoirs; Golf Course; Alumni nominated for Board of Trustees; Ralph Arnold elected ot Board of Trustees, 1914 Dec 28 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Reelection of Wm. Babcock and Charles P. Eells to Board of Trustees; Naval Architecture course; Graduate students exempted from fees; City of Palo Alto lease; Lane Library - purchase of adjoining land; Memorial Church mosaics; VinaRanch; Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific stock; John Hall - purchase of land; Dr. Branner's resignation as president, 1915 Jan 29 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Letters (1 each) of Mr. and Mrs. Stanford offered for sale; Galveston Harrisburg and San Antonio second mortgage bonds; Footbridge over San Francisquito Creek; Payment for Memorial Church mosaics; T.W. Stanford - supplementary funds for books on psychic research; Limitation of students; Hemphill shell collection - gift, 1915 Feb 26 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Calistoga Springs; Statue, "Family Group," removed from Quad; Flugel library; Swimming pool for women; August Berner gift of Vega collection of Mexican mss; Portrait of Trustee Henry C. Dodge accepted, 1915 Mar 26 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Barn from family residence property moved near corporation yard to house faculty horses; Footbridge across San Francisquito Creek; Dept. of Anatomy; Durham Ranch, Butte Co. road rights; T.W. Stanford; Dept. of Practical Sculpture: Rupert Schmid petitioned to create new dept; Notice of Completion of Work (stone work on Memorial Church) [photocopy], 1915 Apr 30 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Dr. Branner asked to continue as president for another year, 1915 May 5 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Encina Club; Student petition for retention of Mr. Quinn as custodian of Encina; Post Office; Request that class plates be permitted to be installed in the Quad; Gift of portrait of Mrs. Stanford by Mrs. Lathrop; Finance Comm. Report; Dr. Branner asked to stay on another year, announcement made at commencement; Notice of Completion of Work (electrial wiring for gymnasium) [photocopy], 1915 May 28 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Charles Lathrop bequest of 10,000 to Med school; Roble Hall matron; Boyd Estate; Notice of completion of work (probably Encina Gym) [photocopy], 1915 Jun 25 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Treasurer's estimate of income, budget; Gift of duplicate library books to the College of the Pacific; House for president; Swimming pool for women; Medical Dept., 1915 Aug 2 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Moving picture house denied place on campus; Mosaics for Memorial Church, 1915 Aug 27 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Isolation hospital; Adolph Barkan gift of a large magnet; Leave of absence for Kellogg and Seward for Belgian Relief Work, 1915 Sep 24 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Election of Dr. Wilbur as President, 1915 Oct 13 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Men's gymnasium; Vina ranch - manager asked to resign; Complete report of ranch made; Fixed limit for cost of fraternity and sorority houses, 1915 Oct 29 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Audit of bonds; Finance Comm. report, 1915 Nov 26 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Appointment Secretary (Employment Office); Caps and gowns forTrustees; San Francisco property; Faculty housing - terms under which University land is leased and loans made for building; Branner made President Emeritus; Dean of Women - Mrs. Allen; Frank Miller - resignation from Board of Trustees, 1915 Dec 31 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Copies of documents re work on campus buildings, wrecking of a portion of the Museum and moving the "resident barn" [copied 2007 at History San Jose], 1915 (Box 11, Folder 18.1)
    - Limitation of men students; Proposal that Stanford lease land for high school; Duties of president asked to be defined - Wilbur; Great Western Power Co. - gift; Gifts from different exhibitors at the Panama-Pacific International Exposition; Vina Winery insurance; Frank Miller asked not to resign from Board; Re Jordan's retirement and peace work, 1916 Jan 28 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Re professors on Carnegie Pensions having any Univ. duties or remaining members of the Academic Council; Lane Hospital Annual Report; Developing the Arboretum; President of Univ. to be invited to all Board of Trustees meetings; Resignation of Frank Miller, 1916 Feb 25 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - A resolution that the Pacific Improvement Co. be voluntarily dissolved. Crocker and Stanford U. to continue together., 1916 Mar 3 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Stanford Golf Club; Japanese Students Club - land lease; Encina Gym - landscaping of grounds; Gifts from exhibitors at Panama - Pacific International Exposition; Printing of President's report; Presidn'ts house site - comm. recommendations; Notice of completion of work on Corporation Shop Building [photocopy]; Notice of completion of work on campus house of H. R. Fairclough [photocopy], 1916 Mar 31 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Univ. land set aside as native plant reserves - proposal; Union High School - land sold for site; University lands set aside as game reserves - proposal; Dept. of Zoology - field station; Northern Electric RR Co; Marin Municipal Water District condemnation suit - lawyers fees, 1916 Apr 28 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Percy T. Morgan elected Trustee, 1916 May 3 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Albany Orphan Asylum suit; Memorial Church mosaics; Carnegie Foundation pension system; David Starr Jordan - retirement, 1916 May 26 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Student loans; American Foreign Securities Co. notes; Boyd estate; Old Chapel (room 100) made into a sate, etc. for English Dept; President's house; Articles of Organization - faculty; Sierra and San Francisco Power Co. - gift to Electrical Engineering Dept. for services, 1916 Jun 30 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Treasurer's report; Lane Medical hospital; Audit of bonds; Great Western Power Co. gifts; Financial Comm; Herbert Hoover, resignation from Board of Trustees; Absentee trustees; Death of Horace Davis; Notice of completion of work on unspecified two story house on campus [photocopy], 1916 Aug 1 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Request for additional staff for president's office; Durham Ranch - sale of 5.4 acres; Bequests, trusts, policy; Frank P. Deering elected to Board of Trustees, 1916 Aug 25 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Frank P. Deering, Trustee; LaneHospital - new Business Office; NewDormitories; Contract for "The Knoll"; Church acoustics, 1916 Sep 29 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Dept. of Military Training; J. Henry Meyer Endowment in honor Antoine Borel; Regulation governing the conduct of examinations; Mrs. B.E. Howard - request for a loan; Letter from Miss Aldeline Oellissier thanking Board of Trustees for memorial to her brother: an ambulance to France; Women's Club House - loan to complete construction; Reelection of Vanderlynn Stow as Trustee, 1916 Oct 27 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Repaint work on museum; Mrs. Charles Lathrop - rental of acreage adjoining her house; Supplying of uniforms to students taking military training; Sly, Stanford Court Apartments: loan; Gift of a gear Generator, 1916 Nov 24 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Vanderlyn Stow reelected Trustee, 1916 Dec 5 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Physical or military training required; Bureau Mines andNavy Dept. contract for research; Outside lighting for Memorial Church; Purchase of Sacramento property; Summer session proposed, 1916 Dec 29 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Registration statistics; Zoology Building renamed Jordan Hall; Request that the charge of the athletic grounds be given to Board of Athletic Control; Contract for "The Knoll" let; Summer session - instructors to teach 3 quarters peryear; Bronze bust of Horace Davis, 1917 Jan 26 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Branner Library; Dept. heads named; Embarcadero Road subway planned; Sly: Stanford Court Apts; Death mask of Mrs. Stanford, 1917 Feb 23 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Stanford Women's Club and Union: petition to charge fee; Suit to remove footbridge across San Francisquito Creek; Establishment of School of Education; J.C. Cebrian gift of Spanish books; Evaluation of museum collection; Letter from Jordan stating which professors didn't receive full salary during the period of the Government suit, 1893-1899; Church and Museum so be under President's office; Notice of Completion of Work on the Art Gallery [photocopy]; Notice of Completion of Work on Encina Hall [photocopy], 1917 Mar 30 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Ione Coal and Iron Co. report; Statement of Jordan, and one by the Board of Trustees upon the U.S. entering the war., 1917 Apr 9 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Approval of the School of Education; Four Quarter System; Standing administration Committee of the faculty; Library funds; Vina Ranch evaluated for sale; Felt Ranch evaluated for sale; Stanford - Palo Alto News; Oldroyd Collection of Shells - terms of purchase., 1917 Apr 27 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Faculty committees; Regulations governing the construction of garages; John M. Stillman retirement., 1917 May 25 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Retirement age - Carnegie Foundation; Carnegie insurance and annuity plan; W.B. Bourn elected trustee., 1917 Jun 23 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Camp Fremont - military contract with Stanford U; Notice of Completion of Work on Art Gallery (ornamental iron work) [photocopy]; Notice of Completion of Work on Art Gallery (painting and finishing) [photocopy], 1917 Jul 26 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Incidental fee: price fixed; Insurance for hospital., 1917 Aug 1 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Wm. B. Bourn acceptance as trustee., 1917 Aug 27 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Stanford Univ. Press: re-setting up of a new press; the question of Mr. Quelle; Finance Committee - investment of funds; Certification of election of William B. Bourn, 1917 Aug 31 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Library Stacks - bids; Loan - Board of Athletic Control; Question of bequest, trusts; Viewbook of Memorial Church commissioned., 1917 Sep 28 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Nomenclature of the Marine Station; Garage for president's house; Durham Ranch - sold; Professor's form. mortgage, taxes, etc.; Sheep Dept. - probable sale; Sly: Stanford Court Apts., 1917 Oct 26 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Spring Valley Water co. :contracts of joint property rights; Dissolution of Vina Agency; C.D. Marks - Acting President; Letter of commendation for Stanford's training of naval doctors and medical corps men., 1917 Dec 7 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Stillman Testimonial Fund to be used for a fellowship; Bid for furnishings for president's house; Contract for heating, electricity, plumbing., 1917 Dec 27 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Sale of Vina and Durham ranches urged; Leave for Dr. Wilbur granted; American flags carried by ambulance units decorated; Letter of appreciation for memorial to Babcock., 1918 Jan 25 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Calistoga Springs Property; Dredging of Searsville Lake; Smithsonian Institution gift of starfishes., 1918 Feb 27 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Searsville Lake - dredging operation, 1918 Apr 5 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Academic Council ruling on men involved in military training; President's budget; University Club agreement; Ames letter of appreciation for help on the death of her husband; Reformatory help for Vina Ranch; Albert Bonnheim prizes; Memorial Resolution passed by Academic Council in honor of Wm Babcock., 1918 Apr 26 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Selah Chamberlain elected to Board of Trustees; J.P. Gillespie gift of stuffed birds and mammals; Gift of 10,000 rounds of 22 caliber short smokeless from Leland Cutler, J.B. Rice, George Presley and others., 1918 May 31 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Deans named; Resignation of Charles Eells as V.P. of Board; Amalgomation of the San Francisco Polyclinic and Stanford Medical School; Formation of a municipal corporation at the University; Certification of election of Selah Chamberlain, 1918 Jun 28 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Clinical Committee; Faculty housing - lease, 1918 Jul 26 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Hospital report of monthly meeting; Water appropriation: application for permit; Flags flown at half-mast for 8 days in respect to the memory of T.W. Stanford., 1918 Aug 30 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Old Roble Hall renamed Sequoia; Gifts; Loan of Chinese art: W. H. Shockly; Loan of South Sea Island implements: J.E. Hewston; T.W. Stanford: memorial resolution., 1918 Sep 27 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Judge George Crothers: Law school scholarship; Mrs. J. E. McDowell - gift to continue Roble Scholarship., 1918 Oct 25 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Andrew D. White memorial resolution; Mayfield: inquiry about leasing land; Appreciation for War Work; Secretaries School; Appointment of attorneys in Australia., 1918 Nov 22 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Recommendation that students who withdrew from school to enter the military service be given certificates; Fees; Proposal to buy mess hall from army to accommounitdate men students; Rocky Mountain Coal and Iron Co; Coryell Investment Co; County roads resolution., 1918 Dec 27 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Appraisal of real property, Stanford Vina Ranch; Summer quarter fees; World War I Memorial; Brooklyn Rapid Transit Company; Lands of Palo Alto Estate set off as natural history reserve; Maintenance of private road in Pacific Grove; Bonding of Institutions to which Government Property is issued; Mayfield lease; Timothy Hopkins browsing room in library; Procedure for requisitions, 1919 Jan 31 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Stillman Testimonial Fund; Gift of books from Stanford to Univ. of Louvain; Vina, Durham Ranches financial report; Civil Engineer, consultant, 1919 Feb 28 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Sperry Flour Co. bonds - proposal to buy; Newfoundland bonds - mature; Attorneys for T.W. Stanford estate; World War I Memorial; Special Development Comm. budgeting procedure - very detailed report of University's financial status; Fitzhugh gift to Lane Hospital; T. T. C. Gregory elected to Board of Trustees., 1919 Mar 28 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Appointment of Department Heads; Mining and metallurgy made a separate department - split off from Geology; Authority to receive custom free property granted Stanford; Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific RR Co. stockholders meeting; Gifts., 1919 Apr 25 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - J. Leroy Nickel reelected Trustee., 1919 May 20 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Fernando Sanford retirement; E.P. Cubberley and L.M. Terman offer $250 each per year to University if Univ. will match the fund and establish a research fellowship; R.O.T.C. contract., 1919 Jun 6 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Leon Sloss elected Assistant Treasurer, 1919 Jul 11 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Bill from McCoy and Gans, attorneys; U.S. Customs service; Organization of Board of Trustees; Vanderlynn Stow. Death., 1919 Aug 1 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Special Development Committee; Disposition of Securities; Audit of Securities., 1919 Aug 29 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - A.E. Roth named comptroller; Cubberley-Terman fellowship for study of gifted children; Elwell scholarship in Electrical Engineering; Japanese Educational Fund - gift of M.T. Ohta; Bertha Hyde Braly Scholarship; George E. Crothers - Law Scholarship; Wm Irwin Weaver Scholarship in chemistry., 1919 Sep 26 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Report on the necessity of increasing salaries and tuition., 1919 Oct 11 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Petition from students asking that tuition payments not be instated until the following Sept. instead of in the coming December; Wilbur requests that the name of the university be officially changed to Stanford University; Stanford Home for Convalescent Children asks that their endowment be held by S.U. Board of Trustees., 1919 Oct 31 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - J.C. Cebrian - gift of Spanish books; J.E. McDowell - Roble Scholarships; Miss Gertrude Gardiner - scholarship gift., 1919 Nov 28 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - George M. Rolph declines nomination as Trustee; Scholarships given., 1919 Dec 26 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Comptroller to take the place of the Business Manager; Sale of personal property from Vina Ranch; Tuition scholarships, grants; Letter to Hoover acknowledging gift of library and stipulations for its charge., 1920 Jan 30 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - John T. Nourse elected Trustee., 1920 Feb 11 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Problem of housing of Chinese students who were not wanted in Encina., 1920 Feb 27 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Commission for Relief in Belgium - two exchange scholarships; Carruther's Farms - lease; Removal of the Corporation Yard and other buildings., 1920 Mar 26 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Bill for system service (accounting); Stanford Home for Convalescent Children lease; Granville (N.Y.) Electric and Gas Co. Consoliunitdated; Request for hotel site on campus; Plan for reorganization of undergraduate instruction submitted by Academic Council., 1920 Apr 30 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Comm. for Relief in Belgium offers third scholarship; Pacific Improvement Co. - directors; Spring Valley Water Co. - purchase of land; Percy T. Morgan memorial resolution; Leon Sloss - Memorial resolution., 1920 May 28 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Dept. heads named; Deans named, 1920 Jun 25 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Leland Cutler named Trustee; M. C. Sloss named Trustee; City of Boston Street Improvement; Ione Coal and Iron Co., 1920 Jul 9 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Stanford Medical School; City of Boston Street Improvement; Pacific Improvement Co. - diminution of capital stock; $150,000 left Univ. by T. W. Stanford, $6,000 per year to go to Psychology Dept., 1920 Aug 2 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Northern Pacific, Great Northern joint bonds; Bids for new dorm - nurses home., 1920 Aug 27 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Scholarships donated., 1920 Sep 24 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Oakland property; National Canners Assoc. - grant to Univ. for study of botulism; W. F. Durand: presented collection of war files of the U.S. Research Information Service in Paris; Vernon Kellogg - gift of his library on entomology and his papers at some future unitdate; U.S. Dept. of Agriculture rental of 5 acres of land on which to breed Blastophage psenes necessary for the fig industry; Stanford Home for Convalescent Children - thanks for lease., 1920 Oct 29 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Housing emergency - need for dormitories and for faculty housing; Charles N. Felton, Jr. bequest of $100,000 to Lane Hospital., 1920 Nov 5 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Stanford Stadium - letter requesting locatioin; Lou Henry Hoover gift of $500 to bind Scholarships and grants., 1920 Nov 26 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Chair of Japanese History and Civilization endowed; first professor, Ichihashi. Comments by Board members re Orientals; The "Palo Alto" tree; Proxies named for stockholders meetings; Faculty houses - terms of lease; Scholarships, grants., 1920 Dec 24 (Box 14, Folder 26)